ExtendBrowser.com

Privacy Policy

Information Collection and Use
------------------------------

These services (website "extendbrowser.com" and browser extensions/add-ons "Safe Web" and "Talk & Write") does not collect personally identifiable information.

Cookies
-------

Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device's internal memory.

This Service use cookies that are necessary for the website to function properly and do not store any personally identifiable information. It also use third-party cookies, which are cookies from a domain different than the domain of the website you are visiting, for our advertising and marketing efforts.

Links to Other Sites
--------------------

These services (website "extendbrowser.com" and browser extensions/add-ons "Safe Web" and "Talk & Write") may contain links to other external sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

Changes to This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

© Copyright 2018-2023 extendbrowser.com
